Whose turn is it?
I'd like one of those little...
Do you have toys? I need a Christmas present for my grandchild.
Do you have anything particular in mind?
It's got to be something that goes "boom"!
How old is the child?
About this tall.
Is it a boy or a girl?
Well...
Well, you must know if your grandchild is a boy or a girl.
Why is that?
Anyway, what's the little one's name?
Hoppenstedt. We're all called Hoppenstedt.
And what's the firstname?
Dickie. Dickie Hoppenstedt.
And it's a girl?
No.
So it's a boy.
No, no, no, no, no!
So what is it then?
I can't tell you exactly.
Well, what does your grandchild wear?
Trousers. Blue trousers.
Well, maybe you've seen them without trousers?
No. Why would I?
Say, what kind of a shop is this anyway?
Please! I only asked the gentleman if his grandchild is a boy or a girl.
If your grandchild has got a willie, one should be able to...
Willie?
For God's sake! Your grandchild doesn't have a willie then.
My grandchild has everything needed!
Healthy parents, a decent home and strict discipline.
So do you sell toys for decent children or not?
This is a new toy for boys and girls from five to ten.
It's very popular. "Let's build a nuclear power plant"
It's fun for the kids and the parents.
It's really something for the entire family.
These are the instructions and those are the parts that need to be assembled.
The burning chamber, uranium core, cooling system, neutron accelerator and the containment structure.
And what is this?
These are trees, houses and cows for the scenery.
Everything has been beautifully made.
Does it go "boom"?
Yes, if you make a mistake, there will be a small explosion.
Of course nothing big. After all, it's for kids.
But it goes "boom" and the cows, little houses, and trees fall over .
It's always a big surprise and a lot of fun.
Would you like to take it?
Yes!
That's ll be 64.50 marks.
You'll get one in the original packaging.
Do you take play money?
No!
Keep the change!
I wish you a merry Christmas and a lot of fun with the nice game!
There used to be more lametta!
This year the tree stays green. Naturally green!
With fresh and natural apples.
Naturally green and eco-friendly.
And when will I get my present?
First, we'll decorate the tree.
Then Dickie will recite a poem, then we'll get the presents in,
then we'll watch the Christmas programme on the first channel,
then we'll unwrap the presents and finally we'll sit down and relax.
No, Walter! First, we'll get the presents in, then Dickie will recite a poem
and we'll unwrap the presents, then we'll tidy up while watching TV
and finally we'll sit down and relax.
And when will I get my present?
Or we could first watch the Christmas programme on the third channel
while unwrapping the presents and afterwards we could sit down and relax.
Dickie, will you please stay in your room?! Santa Claus will be very angry if you don't listen!
There used to be more lametta!
This year the tree is green and eco-friendly.
Merry Christmas! Let's go! Grampa will help me a little
and Dad will turn on the Christmas lights.
Yes!
Merry Christmas!
What?
Dickie, where are you?
Merry Christmas, my darling!
Merry Christmas! Oops!
Dickie would like to recite a poem for us.
Clip, clap! Chicken crap!
No, not that one!
Let's unwrap the presents!
Who could that be?
Come in!
Well, Dickie!
Dickie!
Look who it is!
Grampa!
I want to have my present now!
Here's your present, Grampa!
And why don't you relax a little?!
Look, Walter! It's a Heinzelmann vacuum blower, in the original packaging!
A tie!
Look, it's a record player!
Now you can always play your favourite records in your room.
Look at the tree!
A tie!
Grampa, don't!
I want to play my record!
Go and look for another socket!
Don't be so nasty!
A tie!
This is really cosy!
Grampa, don't! Come sit down and watch TV with us!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Grampa, why don't you have a look at the tree instead?!
I am!
Is Dad going to play the nice new game with Dickie?
Look, Dickie! "Let's build a nuclear power plant"
There are trees, houses, and cows. They'd like to have a nice nuclear power plant.
And this is where we'll build it.
Alas, if only it was Christmas everyday.
This is the little neutron accelerator, this is the burning chamber...Dickie!
Don't knock over the cow!
And now we're going to carefully insert the tiny uranium core into the burning chamber
and the containment structure goes on top.
Done!
Can Mum watch, too?
If we made a mistake, it should go "boom" now.
Why "boom"?
For God's sake! It just goes "boom"!
Then all the houses and cows fall over.
Fantastic!
But it doesn't go "boom"!
It went "boom"!
Lovely!
The Hoppenstedt family would like to wish you a merry Christmas!
Is this really necessary?
Yes, it is. After all, it's a game for kids
and Christmas is a holiday for the kids.
Let's cover it up.
Dad, we're proud of you!
I don't want to deal with these squares on Christmas Eve.
Alright, let's sit down and relax!
Let's tidy up first!
And you're going to bed now, Dickie! It's best to leave the party when it's still fun.
Let's just put it all in the staircase! Let's see if the coast is clear!
Hello? Do you need a Santa Claus?